# Leonardo Rodriguez

Remote Web3 Developer

#### Contact Info

Email: leo@fullstackleo.net Mobile Phone: +1 512 312 8481 Location: Eagle Pass, Texas, USA



#### **Summary**

I'm a high-energy and knowledge thirsty Remote Web3 Developer with 15 years of experience in fullstack development, business management, and creative direction. I am now building Web3 dApps using tech like Solidity, Hardhat, Foundry, and EVM chains (Ethereum, Polygon, BSC). Frontend with React/Next.js, backend with Node.js/TypeScript. I'm skilled with ERC-20/721/1155, Metamask, WalletConnect, The Graph, IPFS, and cross-chain tools. Secure, gas-efficient, end-to-end dApp development is at your service.

I speak native English and Spanish. 🚹 🥌

#### **Portfolios**

- Full Stack Dev: https://fullstackleo.net
- Web Dev, Design, Writing: https://idealeo.net
- GitHub: https://github.com/fullstackleo777

## **Skills**

- Deployment: Linux (Ubuntu, CentOS, RHEL), AWS, GCP, Windows Azure, Docker, Podman, CI/CD
- 🖥 Database: MySQL, NoSQL, SQLite, MariaDB, PostgreSQL, Database Visualizers
- 🧠 Back End: Linux, Bash Scripting, Cron Jobs, SSH, Node.js, PHP, Python, REST API, Autho
- Front End: XML, HTML, CSS/SCSS/SASS, Javascript, Organic SEO, Frameworks (Vue.js, Svelte, React.js)
- 💚 Open Source Software: Server (Apache, NGINX, Lighttpd, ffmpeg), Productivity (OpenOffice, LibreOffice)
- Creative Software: Adobe (Photoshop, Illustrator, InDesign, Premiere Pro), Open Source (Inkscape, Gimp)
- 🔐 Server Security: Firewalled, SSL/TLS, Fail2Ban, SSH Keys, Argon2, IP White/Blacklisting
- DNS Security: DNSSEC, DDOS Protection, Secure Cache, DNS Proxy, DNS Firewall Content Management Systems: HubSpot, Wordpress, Wix, Squarespace, Drupal
- **© eCommerce Platforms:** WP WooCommerce, Magento CE, Shopify, Thirty Bees, Wix, Squarespace
- 🛠 Dev Tooling: GIT (GitHub, GitLab, GiTea), VSCodium, VSCode, Vim, Nano, DIFF, Chrome DevTools
- 🧖 Project Management: Agile, Scrum, Lean, BPM



# **Work Experience**

# Remote Freelance Full Stack Developer at Freelance from January 2016 to December 2024

Since the tech industry is very unpredictable, when I don't have a full time job, I work as a freelancer. In this position, I planned/built/maintained full stack development projects (LAMP, MERN, Wordpress, Shopify), designed brand identities using Photoshop/Illustrator/GIMP/Inkscape, developed for web/mobile using HTML/CSS/SASS/Javascript/Node.js/Vue.js/VSCodium/PHP, designed custom print projects, managed business (accounting, sales, client relations), and led teams of freelancer talent to successful project completion.

## Remote QA Specialist and Web Developer at Education Strategy Consulting, INC. from June 2021 to November 2023

Office Location: Charlottesville, Virginia | Phone: +1 434 961 2584 | Website: https://escmatrix.com

In this role, I scrutinized the company's Java/R/Podman/Node.js/HTML/CSS/SASS/Javascript/PostgreSQL web development process, QA tested big data web apps on varied environments (AWS, Localhost, BrowserStack), unit tested ESC's proprietary development framework, wrote technical documentation, kept track of ongoing issues/bugs across multiple projects, QA tested big data renders via automated tests, and QA tested data manually on LibreOfficeCalc/WebApp.

# Full Stack Developer at PetroPages, INC. from July 2018 to April 2021

Office Location: Webster, TX | Phone: +1 281 316 0353 | Website: https://petropages.com

Onsite, I worked on enterprise & medium business scale projects, secured servers (Linux, Ubuntu, CentOS, Azure, AWS, GCP), encrypted databases (MySQL, MariaDB), shielded REST API endpoints, hardened/encrypted/sanitized/speed-optimized digital products (LetsEncrypt, Fail2Ban, and more!), executed the company-wide switch to GIT version control with CI/CD along with Adrian (CTO), converted front-end mockup designs into HTML/CSS/JavaScript/PHP/Wordpress, executed architecture updates/upgrades (LAMP, GCP, AWS, Azure), crafted HubSpot marketing campaigns, and maintained/troubleshooted/debugged back-end programming (PHP and .NET).

### Business Manager at SignDepotATX from December 2015 to January 2017

Office Location: Austin, TX | Phone: +1 512 219 8000 | Website: https://signdepotatx.com

I began as a graphic designer setting up print files but was promoted to business manager once I started talking to clients/prospects and increasing sales volume. As manager, I managed interns/designers/production/shop workflows, created sales training manuals with Fernando which increased sales, maintained vendor/client relations, designed signage/branding/marketing material using Photoshop/Illustrator, executed organic SEO campaigns on Magento Store, sent out mass communications using MailChimp, and created successful marketing campaigns.

# Creative Director at Image Master Group - A Division of XL Sales & Marketing, LLC. from February 2012 to November 2015

Office Location: Austin, TX | Phone: +1 512 365 0135 | Website: https://imagemastergroup.com

Along with Jose (CEO), I designed company catalogs, created sales presentations for the sales team, created digital graphics for web use, art directed creative marketing campaigns, designed marketing material/promo videos/TV ads/social media imagery/signage/ambient event imagery using Photoshop/Illustrator/Premiere/Sparkle, developed company website using Wix, pushed mass communications via Constant Contact, and developed brochure websites for clientele using Notepad++/HTML/CSS/JavaScript/PHP/WHM with cPanel hosting.

### **Education**